Guide to the Ernest Nagel Papers, 1925-1982 ASP.2020.01
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Correspondence with Organizations, 1928-1949; II.
  - Partisan Review, 1938-1943 (Box 6, Folder 61)
  - Philosophic Abstracts, 1939 (Box 6, Folder 62)
  - Princeton University, 1947-1949 (Box 6, Folder 63)
  - Queens College Dept. of Physics, 1942 (Box 6, Folder 64)
  - Science and Society Quarterly, 1936 (Box 6, Folder 65)
  - Scripta Mathematica, 1941 (Box 6, Folder 66)
  - Society for Ethical Culture in the City of New York, 1947 (Box 6, Folder 67)
  - Teachers Insurance and Annuity Association of America, 1937-1939 (Box 6, Folder 68)
  - Tomorrow Magazine, 1946 (Box 6, Folder 69)
  - United States Customs Service (Treasury Department), 1938 (Box 6, Folder 70)
  - United States Department of Agriculture, 1938 (Box 6, Folder 71)
  - University of California Los Angeles, 1936 (Box 6, Folder 72)
  - University of Chicago Press, 1938 (Box 6, Folder 73)
  - University of Wisconsin Science and Civilization Symposium, no date (Box 6, Folder 74)
  - Who's Who in American Education, 1936 (Box 6, Folder 75)
  - Young Men's Hebrew Association, 1938-1939 (Box 6, Folder 76)
- Topical Files, 1925-1980; III.
  Series III. Topical Files include documentation of offprints, reviews, and comments on scholarly articles by Nagel as well as information and newsclippings that document his participation in the national teach-in on the Vietnam War in 1965.
  - Article Offprints and Drafts, 1950-1971 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Article Offprints and Drafts, 1950-1971 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Certificates and Honorary Degrees, 1962-1964 (Oversize 1)
  - Cohen, Mary Memorial Program, 1945 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Cookeville, Tennessee Rotary Club, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Curriculum Vitae, no date (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Democratic Issues Conference (Palo Alto, CA.) Clippings and Photographs, 1960 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Dewitt Clinton High School (Manhattan) Commencement Program, 1919 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Finances and Travel, 1924-1947 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Get Well Letters, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Godell's Proof Book Reviews and Comments, 1958-1965 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - National Teach-In on the Vietnam War: Background Information, 1965 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - National Teach-In on the Vietnam War Newsclippings, 1965 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - National Teach-In on the Vietnam War: Program, May 15, 1965 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Otto Von Bismarck and Charles Dickens Newsclippings, 1910-1929 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Photographs, c. 1960s (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Reviews and Comments on Publications, 1961-1962 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Reviews and Comments on Publications, 1961-1962 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Tennessee Tech Club Sigma XI National Lecture program and Newsclippings, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 18)